1	The	the	D	1	O
2	Vivaldi	Vivaldi	R	1	I-Hotel
3	Hotel	Hotel	R	1	I-Hotel
4	,	,	O	1	O
5	quaint	quaint	G	1	O
6	&	&	C	1	O
7	friendly	friendly	G	1	O

1	The	the	D	1	O
2	Vivaldi	Vivaldi	R	1	I-Hotel
3	Hotel	Hotel	R	1	I-Hotel
4	(	(	O	1	O
5	Puteaux	Puteaux	R	1	I-Location
6	,	,	O	1	O
7	France	France	R	1	I-Location
8	)	)	O	1	O
9	is	be	V	1	O
10	in	in	P	1	O
11	walking	walk	V	1	O
12	distance	distance	N	1	O
13	to	to	P	1	O
14	the	the	D	1	O
15	metro	metro	N	1	O
16	(	(	O	1	O
17	Paris	Paris	R	1	I-Location
18	)	)	O	1	O
19	.	.	O	1	O

1	Although	although	P	1	O
2	the	the	D	1	O
3	room	room	N	1	O
4	was	be	V	1	O
5	small	small	G	1	O
6	it	it	Q	1	O
7	was	be	V	1	O
8	clean	clean	G	1	O
9	and	and	C	1	O
10	quite	quite	A	1	O
11	servicable	servicable	G	1	O
12	(	(	O	1	O
13	we	we	Q	1	O
14	spent	spend	V	1	O
15	most	most	G	1	O
16	days	day	N	1	O
17	sight	sight	G	1	O
18	·	·	N	1	O
19	seeing	see	V	1	O
20	in	in	P	1	O
21	Paris	Paris	R	1	I-Location
22	.	.	O	1	O

1	We	we	Q	1	O
2	were	be	V	1	O
3	treated	treat	V	1	O
4	to	to	P	1	O
5	a	a	D	1	O
6	full	full	G	1	O
7	breakfast	breakfast	N	1	O
8	daily	daily	A	1	O
9	and	and	C	1	O
10	the	the	D	1	O
11	staff	staff	N	1	O
12	was	be	V	1	O
13	friendly	friendly	G	1	O
14	and	and	C	1	O
15	very	very	A	1	O
16	patient	patient	N	1	O
17	.	.	O	1	O

1	Special	special	G	1	O
2	thank	thank	N	1	O
3	you	you	Q	1	O
4	(	(	O	1	O
5	s	s	N	1	O
6	)	)	O	1	O
7	to	to	P	1	O
8	the	the	D	1	O
9	guest	guest	N	1	O
10	services	service	N	1	O
11	associates	associate	V	1	O
12	Oliver	Oliver	R	1	I-Person
13	&	&	C	1	O
14	Marjoleine	Marjoleine	R	1	I-Person
15	.	.	O	1	O

1	They	they	Q	1	O
2	were	be	V	1	O
3	both	both	D	1	O
4	helpful	helpful	N	1	O
5	in	in	P	1	O
6	providing	provide	V	1	O
7	directions	direction	N	1	O
8	and	and	C	1	O
9	general	general	G	1	O
10	info	info	N	1	O
11	.	.	O	1	O

1	My	my	Q	1	O
2	wife	wife	N	1	O
3	and	and	C	1	O
4	I	i	Q	1	O
5	especially	especially	A	1	O
6	enjoyed	enjoy	V	1	O
7	speaking	speaking	N	1	O
8	with	with	P	1	O
9	Oliver	Oliver	R	1	I-Person
10	,	,	O	1	O
11	and	and	C	1	O
12	exchanging	exchange	V	1	O
13	our	our	Q	1	O
14	respective	respective	G	1	O
15	views	view	N	1	O
16	on	on	P	1	O
17	life	life	N	1	O
18	in	in	P	1	O
19	France	France	R	1	I-Location
20	and	and	C	1	O
21	the	the	D	1	O
22	U.S.	U.S.	R	1	I-Location
23	I	i	Q	1	O
24	do	do	V	1	O
25	not	not	A	1	O
26	know	know	V	1	O
27	when	when	O	1	O
28	we	we	Q	1	O
29	will	will	O	1	O
30	get	get	V	1	O
31	to	to	P	1	O
32	France	France	R	1	I-Location
33	(	(	O	1	O
34	Europe	Europe	R	1	I-Location
35	)	)	O	1	O
36	again	again	A	1	O
37	,	,	O	1	O
38	but	but	C	1	O
39	we	we	Q	1	O
40	will	will	O	1	O
41	definitely	definitely	A	1	O
42	consider	consider	V	1	O
43	the	the	D	1	O
44	Vivaldi	Vivaldi	R	1	I-Hotel
45	Hotel	Hotel	R	1	I-Hotel
46	again	again	A	1	O
47	.	.	O	1	O

